Guide to the Irish Repertory Theatre Records AIA.080
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I. Production Materials, 1988-2010; 9.5 Linear Feet in 14 manuscript boxes, 2 record cartons, 3 oversize flat boxes; 98 Gigabytes in 24,739 computer files; 25 VHS; 20 Digital_Betacam; 12 CDs
  - 2009-2010 Season -- The Irish…And How They Got That Way (Box 12, Folder 14, Box 32, Folder 11, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_45)
  - 2009-2010 Season -- 2010 Benefit -- Brigadoon (Box 12, Folder 15, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_66)
  - 2009-2010 Season -- New Works Reading Series (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - 2010-2011 Season -- 2011 Benefit -- Camelot (Box 12, Folder 17, Box 32, Folder 11, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_67)
  - 2010-2011 Season -- Banished Children of Eve (Box 12, Folder 18, Box 32, Folder 11, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_48)
  - 2010-2011 Season -- St. Nicholas (Box 12, Folder 19, Box 32, Folder 11, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_51)
  - 2010-2011 Season -- Molly Sweeney (Box 12, Folder 20, Box 32, Folder 10, Box Shared Tamiment 002, Folder 2, Box Electronic records, E-records [TW_AIA_80_ER_49)
  - 2010-2011 Season -- A Child's Christmas in Wales (Box 12, Folder 21, Box 32, Folder 10, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_47)
  - 2010-2011 Season -- My Scandalous Life (Box 13, Folder 1, Box 32, Folder 10, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_50)
  - 2010-2011 Season -- The Shaughraun (Box 13, Folder 2, Box 32, Folder 10, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_52)
  - 2010-2011 Season -- Tryst (Box 13, Folder 3, Box 32, Folder 8, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_53)
  - 2011-2012 Season -- Noċtú (Box 13, Folder 4, Box 32, Folder 8, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_57)
  - 2011-2012 Season -- Dancing at Lughnasa (Box 13, Folder 5, Box 32, Folder 8, Box Shared Tamiment 003, Folder 4, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_55)
  - 2011-2012 Season -- A Child's Christmas in Wales (Box 13, Folder 6, Box 32, Folder 9)
  - 2011-2012 Season -- New Girl in Town (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - 2011-2012 Season -- Beyond The Horizon (Box 13, Folder 8, Box 32, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_54)
  - 2011-2012 Season -- Give Me Your Hand (Box 13, Folder 9, Box 32)
  - 2011-2012 Season -- Man and Superman (Box 13, Folder 10, Box 32, Folder 9, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_56)
  - 2011-2012 Season -- New Works Reading Series (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 2011-2012 Season -- 2012 Benefit -- Oliver! (Box 13, Folder 11, Box 32, Folder 9, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_68)
  - 2012-2013 Season -- A Celebration of Harold Pinter (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - 2012-2013 Season -- The Freedom of the City (Box 13, Folder 13, Box 32, Folder 6)
  - 2012-2013 Season -- Airswimming (Box 13, Folder 14, Box 32, Folder 6)
  - 2012-2013 Season -- Donnybrook! The Musical of The Quiet Man (Box 13, Folder 15, Box 32, Folder 7)
  - 2012-2013 Season -- For Love (Box 13, Folder 16, Box 32, Folder 7)
  - 2012-2013 Season -- The Songs I Love So Well (Box 40, Cd TW_AIA_080_530, Box 32, Folder 8)
  - 2012-2013 Season -- Who's Your Daddy? (Box 13, Folder 17, Box 32, Folder 7)
  - 2012-2013 Season -- Gibraltar (Box 13, Folder 18, Box 32, Folder 7)
  - 2012-2013 Season -- The Weir (Box 13, Folder 19, Box 32, Folder 7, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_59)
  - 2012-2013 Season -- 25th Anniversary Gala -- Something Wonderful! (Box 13, Folder 20, Box 32, Folder 7, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_69)
  - 2012-2013 Season -- It's A Wonderful Life (Box 13, Folder 21, Box 32, Folder 7, Folder 20, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_58)
  - 2013-2014 Season -- Remembering Seamus (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - 2013-2014 Season -- A Mind-Bending Evening of Beckett (Box 13, Folder 23, Box 32, Folder 5)
  - 2013-2014 Season -- Juno and the Paycock (Box 13, Folder 24, Box 32, Folder 4, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_60)
  - 2013-2014 Season -- It's A Wonderful Life (Box 13, Folder 25, Box 32, Folder 4)
  - 2013-2014 Season -- 2014 Benefit -- The Spectacular Songs of Lerner and Loewe (Box 13, Folder 26, Box 32, Folder 5)
  - 2013-2014 Season -- Sea Marks (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - 2013-2014 Season -- Transport (Box 13, Folder 28, Box 32, Folder 4)
  - 2014-2015 Season -- Port Authority (Box 13, Folder 29, Box 32, Folder 3)
  - 2014-2015 Season -- A Christmas Memory (Box 13, Folder 30, Box 32, Folder 5)
  - 2014-2015 Season -- 2015 Benefit -- Yeats: The Celebration (Box 13, Folder 31, Box 32, Folder 3)
  - 2014-2015 Season -- The Weir (Box 13, Folder 32, Box 32, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder Shared Special Collections 003)
  - 2014-2015 Season -- The Belle of Belfast (Box 13, Folder 33, Box 32, Folder 3)
  - 2014-2015 Season -- Da (Box 14, Folder 1, Box 32, Folder 3, Box Shared Tamiment 003)
  - 2014-2015 Season -- Meet Me at the Square: Farewell Benefit at the 22nd Street Location (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 2015-2016 Season -- The Quare Land (Box 14, Folder 3, Box 32, Folder 2)
  - 2015-2016 Season -- The Burial At Thebes (Box 14, Folder 4, Box 32, Folder 2)
  - 2015-2016 Season -- A Child's Christmas in Wales (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 2015-2016 Season -- Shining City (Box 14, Folder 6, Box 32, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - 2015-2016 Season -- 2016 Benefit -- Finian's Rainbow (Box Shared Tamiment 003, Folder 2, Box 14, Folder 8)
  - 2015-2016 Season -- A Celebration of Harold Pinter (Box 14, Folder 7, Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Unspecified productions, Undated (Box 34, Cassette 080.0039, Box Shared Tamiment 002, Folder 1, Box Shared Tamiment 003, Folder 3)
  - Unspecified Yeats production, Undated (Box 33, Cassette 080.0002-080.0003)
- Series II. Literary Department Records, 2005-2014; 3.8 Linear Feet in 9 manuscript boxes
  This series is arranged in two subseries, Subseries II. A. Selected Plays and Subseries II.B. Rejected Script Files.
  This series documents the work of the Literary Department in evaluating submitted scripts and choosing works for the New Works Reading Series. Material in this series consists entirely of paper.
  - Subseries II. A. Selected Plays, 2006-2014; 1.7 Linear Feet in 4 manuscript boxes
    This subseries is arranged in chronological order by year and month in which the plays were performed by the IRT.
    This subseries includes scripts chosen as part of the New Works Readings Series.
    - 2006 (Box 14, Folder 9-19, Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 2007 (Box 15, Folder 2-12, Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 2008 (Box 16, Folder 1-6)
    - 2009 (Box 16, Folder 7-9, Box 17, Folder 1-5)
    - 2010 (Box 17, Folder 6-12)
    - 2011 (Box 17, Folder 13-14)
    - 2012 (Box 17, Folder 15-16)
    - 2013 (Box 17, Folder 17-18, Box 18, Folder 1)
    - 2014 (Box 18, Folder 2-4)
  - Subseries II. B. Rejected Script Files, 2005-2014; 2.1 Linear Feet in 5 manuscript boxes
    This subseries consists of script files submitted for the New Works Readings Series that were rejected by the IRT. The files include scripts, cover letters, curricula vitae, correspondence with authors, and reader reports.
    The files in this subseries are loosely arranged in numerical order according to numbers assigned to each script as it was received by the Literary Department.
    - 0643-0715, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 5-15)
    - 0716-0763, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 1-9)
    - 0796-06145, unnumbered files, 2005-2010, undated (Box 20, Folder 1-14)
    - Unnumbered files, 2006, undated (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - Reader reports, 2005-2014, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Rejection letters, 2006-2013 (Box 21, Folder 4-12, Box 22, Folder 1-10, Box 23, Folder 1-2)
- Series III. Administrative Records, 1990-2013; 3.75 Linear Feet in 5 manuscript boxes and 1 oversize flat box; 203.1 Gigabytes in 57,715 computer files
  This series is arranged in five subseries: Subseries III. A. General Administrative Records, Subseries III. B. Producing Director Records, Subseries III. C. General Manager Records, Subseries III. D. Membership Manager Records, and Subseries III.E. Marketing Department Records.
  This series documents various administrative offices and activities of the IRT, including the Producing Director, the General Manager, the Membership Manager, and the Marketing Department. Material in this series consists of both paper and born-digital material and includes correspondence, reports, budgets, photographs, and blueprints and floor plans.
  - Subseries III. A. General Administrative Records, 1990-2013; 1.3 Linear Feet in 3 manuscript boxes
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by format or topic.
    This subseries documents the IRT's cooperation with labor unions representing performers in New York City and the work of the IRT's Board of Directors. This subseries includes correspondence and contracts. Labor unions include the Actors' Equity Association, the United Scenic Artists, Local 802 Associated Musicians of Greater New York, and the Stage Directors and Choreographers Society. Material documenting the work of the Board includes correspondence and meeting agenda and minutes.
    - Actors' Equity Association, 2001-2010 (Box 23, Folder 3-10)
    - Board of Directors, 1994-2005 (Box 23, Folder 11-14, Box 24, Folder 1-6)
    - Budgets, 1988-1992 (Box 24, Folder 7-8)
    - Fundraising for new theater space, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - General correspondence, 1993-2010 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - The Irish…And How They Got That Way, 1997-2009 (Box 24, Folder 11-13)
    - Local 802, Associated Musicians of Greater New York, 2004-2010 (Box 24, Folder 14-15)
    - Materials for the Arts, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 16-17, Box 25, Folder 1-3)
    - New York City Department of Cultural Affairs, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Stage Directors and Choreographers Society, 1999-2009 (Box 25, Folder 5-7)
    - The Streets of New York -- Westport County Playhouse, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Subsidiary and other royalty agreements, 2003-2009 (Box 25, Folder 9-12)
    - United Scenic Artists, Local USA-829, 2004-2010 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Subseries III. B. Producing Director Records, 1994-2003; 0.2 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box; 51.32 Megabytes in 1,159 computer files
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by production title, topic, or format of material.
    This subseries documents the work of Ciarán O'Reilly, co-founder and Producing Director of the IRT. Materials consists of paper and born-digital material and includes correspondence, budgets, notes, box office reports, and scripts. Correspondence includes negotiations with the Actors' Equity Association, requests for and acknowledgements of financial support for productions and the IRT, and licensing for scripts. This subseries contains material regarding the production of Grandchild of Kings, a production adapted from Sean O'Casey's autobiographies, directed by Harold Prince. This subseries also includes letters from O'Reilly to IRT members and sponsors, labor unions, and directors of productions at the IRT, including Tony Walton and Frank McCourt.
    - Alive, Alive Oh!, 1991 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_74)
    - The Au Pair Man, 1992 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_101)
    - Bailegangaire, 2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_75)
    - Bedbound, 2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_76)
    - Benefits, 2001-2002 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_77)
    - Biographies, Undated (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_78)
    - Building fund, 1994 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_79)
    - A Celtic Christmas, 2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_70)
    - Contact sheets, 2001 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_80)
    - The Dead, 1995-1997 (Box 25, Folder 14-16)
    - Dear Liar, 1999 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_81)
    - Donal Donnelly project, 2001 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_82)
    - Endwords, 1990 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_83)
    - English That For Me, 1989 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_84)
    - Financial documents, 1988-1995 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_85)
    - General correspondence, 1987-1995 (Box 25, Folder 17, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_86)
    - General files, 1989-2015 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_87)
    - Grandchild of Kings, 1991-1995 (Box 3, Folder 17, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_88)
    - The Heart's a Wonder, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 18, Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_102)
    - I Do Not Like Thee, Dr. Fell, 1981-1988 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_89)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1995 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_103)
    - The Importance of Being Oscar, 2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_104)
    - The Irish...and How They Got That Way, 2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_105)
    - Joyicity and Frankly Brendan, 1992 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_90)
    - A Life, 2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_71)
    - The Madame MacAdam Travelling Theatre, 1992 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_106)
    - Making History, 1981-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_91)
    - The Matchmaker, 2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_107)
    - Meet Me in St. Louis, 1990 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_92)
    - The Mother of All Behans, 1992-1994 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_108)
    - Patron lists, 1994 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_93)
    - Philadelphia, Here I Come, 1988-1990 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_94)
    - The Picture of Dorian Gray, 2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_109)
    - Pigtown, 2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_95)
    - The Playboy of the Western World, 2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_110)
    - The Plough and the Stars, 1988 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_111)
    - Save It For the Stage: The Life of Reilly, 2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_96)
    - Sea Marks, 1989-1990 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_97)
    - Seconds Out, 1992 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_98)
    - Shadowtackle, 1991 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_99)
    - Single performances, 1996-2002 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - The Streets of New York, 2003; 1794 kilobytes in 36 documents. (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_112)
    - That and the Cup of Tea, 2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_100)
    - Translations, 1992 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_113)
    - A Tribute to Samuel Beckett, 1990-1991 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_72)
    - Unspecified performance documents, Undated (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_114)
    - The Weir, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - A Whistle in the Dark, 1989-1990 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_73)
    - Yeats: A Celebration, 1989 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_115)
    - Yeats tribute, 1988-1995 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Subseries III. C. General Manager Records, 1997-2004; 0.5 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box and 1 oversize flat box; 10.34 Gigabytes in 5,365 computer files
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by production title, topic, format, or by the name of file's creator.
    This subseries documents the work of two of the General Managers of the IRT, Shelley A. Troupe and Meridith Sommers. Responsibilities of this role documented in this subseries include managing day-to-day activities of the IRT, organizing the IRT's annual benefit, participating in advertising and development campaigns, managing the box office, and tracking compliance with the Actor's Equity Association (AEA) contracts. Material in this subseries consists of paper and born-digital material and includes correspondence, budgets, audits, contracts, photographs, box office reports, meeting agenda and minutes, and promotional material. This subseries includes Board of Directors meeting agenda and minutes and correspondence with the AEA, IRT members and sponsors, vendors, and insurance providers.
    - Actors' Equity Association, 1998-2004 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_117)
    - Advertising, 2002-2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_118)
    - Assorted production stills, 1988-2008 (Box 26, Folder 1-2, Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Audits, 2001-2004 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_119)
    - Bailegangaire, 2002 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_120)
    - Benefits, 2001-2009 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_121)
    - Board of Directors, 2001-2004 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_122)
    - Box office, 2002-2004 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_123)
    - Budgets, 2000 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_124)
    - Celtic Christmas, 2002 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_125)
    - The Colleen Bawn, 2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_152)
    - Computer system manual, 2000-2001 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_126)
    - Contracts, 2004 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_127)
    - Dear Liar, 1998-1999 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_128)
    - Development, 1999-2004 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_129)
    - Eden, 2003-2004 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_130)
    - Finian's Rainbow, 2003-2004 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_131)
    - Foley, 2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_132)
    - Frank McCourt memorial event photographs, 2009 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_133)
    - Human Resources, 2001-2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_134)
    - The Importance of Being Oscar, 2001-2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_153)
    - Invoices, 1998-2002 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_135)
    - The Irish...And How They Got That Way, 2002-2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_154)
    - Irish Repertory Theatre history, 2002-2008 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_136)
    - Irish Repertory Theatre logos, 2001 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_137)
    - Let's Put on a Show, 2004 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_138)
    - Marketing, 2002 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_139)
    - Materials for the Arts, 2002 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_140)
    - Membership, 2000 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_141)
    - 1996-1997 season sales (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_116)
    - Pauline Flanagan, Undated (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_142)
    - Peg O' My Heart, 2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_143)
    - Photographs for 20th anniversary gala, 1988-2008 (Box 26, Folder 3-6)
    - Pigtown, 2002 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_144)
    - The Playboy of the Western World -- Program, 2002 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_155)
    - Printing spreadsheet, 2004; 21 kilobytes in 1 document. (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_145)
    - Productions, 2002 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_146)
    - Rental agreements, 1997-1999 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_147)
    - Royalties, 2002 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_148)
    - Season subscriptions, 2001-2003 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_149)
    - Sommers, Meridith, 2002 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_150)
    - The Streets of New York, Undated (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_156)
    - Templates and logos, 2002-2004 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_151)
    - Tina Flaherty party photographs, Undated (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_157)
    - Triptych, 2004 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_158)
    - Troupe, Shelley, 1997-2001 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_159)
    - 2011-2012 capital campaign statement (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Unspecified event photographs, 2005 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_160)
    - Video, 2002 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_161)
    - Website, 2003-2004 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_162)
  - Subseries III.D. Membership Manager Records, 2001-2009; 125 Megabytes in 91 computer files
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by topic.
    This subseries documents the work of two of Membership Managers of the IRT, Heather Kray and Eric Scott. Responsibilities of this role documented in this subseries include maintaining relationships with current theatre members as well as with advertisers. This subseries consists entirely of born-digital material and includes correspondence, spreadsheets, and promotional material.
    - High level member letters, 2001 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_163)
    - Mailings, 2001-2006 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_164)
    - Membership, 2000-2005 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_165)
    - Patron's Circle, 2004-2009 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_166)
  - Subseries III.E. Marketing Department Records, 1988-2016; 0.2 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box; 192.6 Gigabytes in 51,099 computer files
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by production title, format, or topic.
    This subseries documents the work of the Marketing Department, including branding, promotion of the IRT and its productions, development of the capital campaign to renovate the theatre from 2014 to 2016, and the creation of a new website in 2012. The material in this subseries consists of paper and born-digital material and includes correspondence, promotional material, spreadsheets, photographs, blueprints, floor plans, and artwork. This subseries contains the Marketing Department's archive of promotional material for individual productions for seasons 2003-2004 to 2016-2017, material detailing the creation of the IRT's new website in 2012, guidelines for IRT branding standards, and artwork used in the creation of promotional material. Material detailing the development of the capital campaign includes a brochure and statement regarding the campaign, photographs and videos used to promote the campaign, and photographs of the theatre before, during, and after the renovation.
    - After the Ball, 2004 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_168)
    - Artwork for 2006-2007 season promotional materials (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_169)
    - Branding, 2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_170)
    - Capital campaign, 2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_171)
    - Closing photographs, 2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_172)
    - Exterior shots for commercial, 2005 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_173)
    - Irish Repertory Theatre photographs, 2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_174)
    - Irish Repertory Theatre promotional advertisement, 2006 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_175)
    - Irish Repertory Theatre video, 2011 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_61)
    - Krapp's Last Tape, 1998 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_177)
    - Major Barbara, 1997 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_178)
    - Marketing Archive -- 2003-2004 Season, 2003-2016 (Box Electronic records, E-records TW_AIA_80_ER_179)